[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many rings were given to humans by Sauron in Lord of the Rings?", "correct_answer": "9", "incorrect_answers": ["5", "7", "11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many eggs does a turkey usually lay?", "correct_answer": "8-15", "incorrect_answers": ["4-12", "6-13", "4-8"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the herb Chamomile literally mean in Greek?", "correct_answer": "Earth apple", "incorrect_answers": ["Small wonder", "Cure for everything", "Angels face"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the earliest movies ever made is A Trip to the Moon  ( 1902 ).  Who wrote and directed this landmark film?", "correct_answer": "George Melies", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Dolby", "Ranier Fassbinder", "Thomas Edison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Female Komodo Dragons can lay eggs without any contact with males.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Mars family were the richest American family of 1988, according to Fortune magazine.  They named one of their most successful products after their horse, who was named what?", "correct_answer": "Snickers", "incorrect_answers": ["Bounty", "MM", "Corny"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This disorder is the abnormal accumulation of cerebrospinal fluid in the ventricles of the brain.", "correct_answer": "Hydrocephalus", "incorrect_answers": ["Spina bifida", "Multiple sclerosis", "Epilepsy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Due to the presence of trace amounts of this chemical emeralds appear green.", "correct_answer": "Chromium", "incorrect_answers": ["Copper", "Mercury", "Zinc"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lawrence Bohune was the first doctor in the British Colony of Virginia. When did he arrive?", "correct_answer": "1610", "incorrect_answers": ["1689", "1704", "1622"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress, best known for playing Ilsa Lund in one of the most popular romantic dramas, defined a kiss as a lovely trick designed by nature to stop speech when words become superfluous.", "correct_answer": "Ingrid Bergman", "incorrect_answers": ["Greta Garbo", "Elizabeth Taylor", "Katherine Hepburn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Salix vitellina is the scientific name of this essence usually given to a horse that appears to sulk, goes into moods and refuses any sort of attention.", "correct_answer": "Willow", "incorrect_answers": ["Wild Rose", "Wild Oat", "Water Violet"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aichmophobia is defined as an abnormal fear of what?", "correct_answer": "pointy objects", "incorrect_answers": ["algebraic equations", "tombstones", "atomic explosives"]}]